Daddy's been working in the garden... again!
Stepfather 3 is a horror, thriller, tv movie film directed by Guy Magar.
After escaping a Puget Sound institution, "Stepfather" Gene Clifford alters his
appearance with plastic surgery and takes on another new identity: Keith Grant.
Moving to Deer View, California, Keith falls for a divorced school principal,
arousing the suspicions of her wheelchair-bound, computer-savvy son.
Keith Grant / The Stepfather, played by Robert Wightman.
Christine Ann Davis, played by Priscilla Barnes.
Jennifer Ashley, played by Season Hubley.
Andy Davis, played by David Tom.
Father Ernest Thomas Brennan, played by John Ingle.
Mr. Thompson, played by Dennis Paladino.
The Stepfather is a 1987 American psychological horror film directed by Joseph
Ruben and starring Terry O'Quinn, Jill Schoelen, and Shelley Hack.
O'Quinn stars as an identity-assuming serial killer who
marries a widow with a teenage daughter.
Having killed his previous family and changed his identity, his murderous
tendencies continue after his stepdaughter becomes suspicious of him.
The film is loosely based on the life of mass murderer John List, although the
plot is more commonly associated with slasher films of the era.
The film was written by Donald E.
Westlake, from a story by Westlake, Carolyn Lefcourt and Brian Garfield (the latter
of Death Wish fame), with an uncredited rewrite by David Loughery.
The film was theatrically released in the United States on January 23, 1987.
It grossed $2.5 million at the box office and was well-received by critics.
It has since gained a cult following and was followed by two slasher
sequels, Stepfather II (1989) and Stepfather III (1992).
A remake, also called The Stepfather, was released in 2009.
The film explores themes of stepfather, sequel, serial killer.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.